One of the things that you really don't want on a job for when you're working from a home office environment is distractions.
It's so easy- and this is actually true whether you work from home or any typical office setting.
But as far as e-mails, and voice mails go, those are kind of your big time consumers if you let them be.
I know for my self, and I've talked to a lot of other people who work at home, who have found that, who has somewhat challenge, when you're constantly checking your e-mail, there's always something coming up that you can do.
And a lot of times it's not the most important thing, but you get sucked into it, and before you know it an hour is gone.
So here I go to my e-mail, oh lets see, okay, yeah, this guy he wants me to write an article for him, this is important I better get back to him.
Oh, okay, he wants to know, oh what do I do, okay, I got to get and see my resume, some writing samples.
You know what, there's an effective way to do things, and an ineffective.
The ineffective way is to just attack everything as soon as it comes.
That's not effective because you'll be- if you do that, you can easily use up eight hours in a day responding to e-mails and voice-mails, and you're not going to get anything done.
What you want to do is completely avoid e-mails and voice-mails if you can, until you're completely done with your most important things for that day that you need to get done.
And if that's not possible, then at least schedule in times, maybe once or twice a day when you will attend voice-mails and e-mails, but don't go over that time.
And anything you can't get done, it probably wasn't the most important thing anyway, so you'll be okay.